(Amy:)Please?
(Sheldon:)Fine.
"As Cooper prepared to depart,
"tears filled Amelia's eyes.
"He took her hand in his
and said, 'I can't stay,
"but I will never forget you.'
"He brushed his fingers
against her cheek,
"then quickly stepped
into the machine.
"'Please don't go,'
she whispered.
"But it was too late.
"The engine hummed to life.
(Bernadette:)But they didn't even kiss.
AMY:
"She turned away,
"wiping her eyes.
"She couldn't bear to watch
"her one chance at true love
disappear forever.
"Then... she felt a strong
hand on her shoulder
"spin her around.
"It was Cooper.
(gasps)
(whispers):
Yes!
"'What about the future?'
asked Amelia.
"He looked deeply into her eyes
and whispered,
"'There is no future
without you.'
"He pulled her in close.
"She began to
tremble all over.